DIMITRIS GEORGAKOPOULOS

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT ME

- dimitris.geo@gmail.com
- (+30) 6948789758
- in dimitris-georgakopoulos
- geoelectrof
- codefarmer.netlify.com

ABOUT

I am a super passionate Front-End Developer with User experience UX in mind and a competent understanding of website design principles. Always willing to learn new technologies and ways to implement the best easy-to-use websites in a short time. Flexible enough to work independently and within a team.

TECH SKILLS

MAIN SKILLS:

















Git













ADDITIONAL SKILLS:

Sanity.io





PROJECTS

Thessaloniki City Virtual Guide



Fully functional webpage built with React . The user is able to filter the highlights of the city by category and see more details on a separate page. Sanity studio was used as content management system.

TECH STACK: React|S, HTML, Sass, Bootstrap, Sanity.io, Framer Motion

Countries of the World





Use of REST Countries API to pull country data and display it. User is able to search for countries, filter countries by region and click on a country to see more detailed information on a separate page.

TECH STACK: Javascript, HTML, CSS

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE



Caretta

https://caretta-print.gr Thessaloniki, Greece | 2009-2022

Web Designer & Web Administrator

2017-2022

- Implementation of WordPress & E-commerce solutions
- Administration and maintenance of existing running solutions

Upper-Intermediate (B2)

• Support of the daily operations of sites as needed

Graphic Designer

2009-2017

EDUCATION

Front-End Developer

Social Hackers Academy, 7 Months Coding Bootcamp

BSc in Applied Informatics

University of Macedonia | Thessaloniki, Greece

LANGUAGES

French Greek **English** Fluent (C2)

INTERESTS

Maternal

Hiking Sailing **Dance**